#### WEBSITE

kevindesignhyde.com

## MOBILE

+1 (733) 773 - 6073

## **EMAIL**

kphyde@gmail.com

## LINKEDIN

/kevin-hyde-54a71416

#### **GITHUB**

/futurethang

# **KEVIN HYDE**

Full-Stack Web Developer with a dedication to creative thinking, problem-solving, and thoughtful user experiences. Extensive career history of collaboration and creative solutions within technical services, sales, business enterprise, and freelance graphic design. Well versed in MERN stack application development and eager dabbler with new tools and technologies.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

HMTL/CSS	MONGO DB	
JAVASCRIPT	MYSQL	••••
NODE.JS	REACT.JS	••••
EXPRESS.JS	ADOBE CC	

# RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

LEAD MEDIA TECHNICIAN UW Medicine 2017 - Present Seattle WA

MEETING TOMORROW Audio Visual Services 2010 - 2016 Chicago IL

GRAPHIC DESIGNER 2005 - Present Freelance Oversee all in-house Audio Visual technology, mitigate and resolve issues, and assist users. ¶ Plan and execute A/V ranging from small meetings to multi-room seminars, hundreds annually. ¶ Train users on web conference technologies. ¶ Quickly assist non-tech-savvy users with friendliness and patience, often in high pressure scenarios.

Pivot-player in rapidly evolving small business environment. Generated \$400k yearly revenue as Account Services Specialist. Innovated Sales Team Systems role, provided analytics, product development, team training sessions, and designed/implemented CRM and phone solutions. ¶ Maintained quality of outsourced solutions, reviewing logistics and negotiations across nation-wide vendor network, averaging 60+% order margins. ¶ Leveraged adaptability and broad skillset to contribute emergency talent to Marketing, IT, Special Events, and Warehouse departments.

Web and Print services for individuals and businesses. ¶ Strategize and execute marketing and communications to find new clients. Provide consultations, research, and detailed bids to customize scope and project options for deadline and budget constraints. ¶ Quickly learn new technologies and techniques to deliver appealing graphics that work in multiple formats and applications

### EDUCATION

U OF WASHINGTON Javascript Full Stack Web Dev Boot Camp

VALPARAISO UNIVERSITY BS in Fine Arts

Intensive full-stack boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js and ReactJS.

Liberal Arts degree with a focus on Visual Arts, Graphic Design and Art History